I'm kicking myself because I sat up there in front of all those people that came out and showed so much love here in Wilmington, Delaware and did not say nothing about Patreon.
Listen, y'all, that just goes to show y'all that your girl is not really about the money because I'd be forgetting to promote my own shit.
Well, if you were there, I appreciate y'all.
You showed so much love that I was so enraptured that I didn't even remember to promote the stuff that I need to be promoting.
So if you have not subscribed to my Patreon, hopefully you will.
The link is right here.
Thank you to the Wilmington Library for hosting me.
I had such a great time as a part of the speaker series and Marla did an incredible job moderating the Q&A and I even got to really read excerpts from my book, Small Doses.
I forgot that I wrote a whole book, but it was just it was nice and y'all showed a lot of love.
I didn't even know that my radio show reaches all the way out to Wilmington, Delaware, but y'all know the song.
We up, we up, we up.
Thank y'all.
Thank you.
Welcome back.